What's wrong, you
came so early in the morning? Is it flag hoisting at school?
Tell the truth, I
know they will give you chocolates. I know
our school singer sings before the flag hoisting
.
Guess what song is being sung, it's
always the same song,
every day, the song is the
country, our own
strength, our own sinner,
our own child, what is it,
Babuji, this is the same
soulful melody, in the air,
mom, take a photo, okay, okay,
mom, it's good, I should
put it on status right away.  I asked
you to wear a white dress, but
my mother didn't let me, madam.
My mother didn't iron it, ma'am.
That's not right, ma'am.
Okay, ma'am, they'll
bring chocolates.
They don't give chocolates because they're not good for children.  [Screaming face] Enough.